Kill me out of this, I'd never hear the end of her!
Time for revenge, my friend.
You ready?
Hamburger Hammer!
Honkata!
Sling tankers!
Skies attack?
Grr!
Ha!
In fact you might say they're grr-grr-grr-ay!
Now all that's left is to stuff the ball man in his coffin!
I mean, goal!
And it'll be two wins in a row for the Foxy Pirates!
Hey, let's work...
together for...
ten seconds.
Okay, fine.
But no longer.
A barrage of red cards in groggy ring!
The second match of our camey back fight has come to a dramatic conclusion!
It's another win for our groggy monsters!
And while the Straw Hats put up a good fight, they were simply no match for our reigning champs!
So, with two wins in a row for the Foxy Pirates and one adorable new doctor on the crew, we must wonder who Captain Foxy will choose next!
Hey wait!
Look!
They're up!
Against all odds, the Straw Hats are back on their feet!
Even after a demoralizing beatdown, the swordsman without his swords and the seven ship stand tall in the face of adversity once again!
Yeah!
You guys!
Why you gotta scare me like that?
The question is, even if they can stand, do they have enough strength left to fight?
I have a little request.
One monster burger, please!
Huh?
Now what could that mean?
Did someone say burgers?
Cause I could go for one.
Is that all you ever think about?
Uh-oh!
Did you hear that?
Our boss has just ordered the famous monster burger!
He-he-he-he-he-he-he-he!
I get that you guys are cheaters and all, but can you at least try to hide it?
Grind them all up like some burger meat,
Size of my pickle, sour or sweet?
One of the toppings!
A head of green lettuce and some fine yellow cheese!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Smash between some big pans, what do I say?
A monster burger for me to eat.
Here it comes! The most terrifying triple attack!
The most horrifying hamburger!
It seems hopeless for the Straw Hats!
But I can't help but think that the Kraggy Monsters
might get handed to Redcart for such a flagrant violation of the rules!
But looking back, what a coincidence!
The referee just happens to be doing some stretches right now!
Oh well, he can't catch everything!
I'm gonna make you turn around!
Luffy, no!
Why not?
Cause they want you to get mad so you'll butt in and do something stupid!
We just gotta grin and fear it, Luffy!
The preparations are complete!
All that's left now is to sit back and enjoy the carnage!
Whatever happens from here on out, don't blame me!
Anyway, looks like they're going straight for the ball man!
Unless he acts fast, he'll be ground and pounded, spliced and diced,
dragged and smashed into a burger patty!
All right then, if you want a cooking battle, you got one.
Though I gotta warn you, I've never cooked scumbags before,
so I can't say how it'll turn out.
P-p-p-p-p-p-p-p! You are mincemeat!
Ba-shun!
proctor?
Proctor?
Proctor waktor?
Stop crushing!
No! Hamburg!
You're gonna pay for that!
Hold up, fatty. Forget about me.
Out of my way, small fry!
I'll cut you!
No-sword style.
Tatsu?
Maki!
Oh no! Saiyan isn't so!
Rick Pan has fallen victim to pickle-spinning blade attack!
Somebody help me! I can't stop spinning!
I can't do this, I need to scare trucks!
I can't do this right!
Bad manner!
Kick course!
Of course!
What?
Not only did they knock Big Pan down,
they knocked him right back up too!
Although Big Pan is indeed on his feet,
I'm not sure if he has any idea where he's at right now.
To make matters worse,
Pickles is looking pretty dazed himself.
Team Foxy is in a real pinch!
Uh-oh! Now Zoro from the Straw Hats is charging in!
Will he be able to overtake Big Pan in his state of confusion?
You're not getting past me!
I've had enough of your crap,
and that goes for the ref too.
The crowd, or rather the ref,
takes a direct hit from the Flying Pickles!
Did Sanji have an ulterior motive, perhaps?
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Red car!
Huh?
Wait a sec!
My whistle and my cards are gone!
You're such a naughty girl.
What can I say?
Old habits die hard!
Oh!
This is bad!
Here they go again!
With victory in their grasp,
the Straw Hats turn on each other!
What a shame!
Here they go again!
With victory in their grasp, the Straw Hats turn on each other!
Ah!
Shame!
A medallion!
Power show!
Incredible!
Big Ben!
What?
No way!
The massive Wu-Tan Warriors!
All right!
We're headed for the Goal Ring!
It can't be!
Goal!
Voilà it in the subscribe-
Cool!
Incredible!
Big Ben!
Is airborne!
All right!
It's at me!
It goes in!
Go, go, go!
Yeah! Way to go!
Yeah, all right! We won!
We won!
I'm so happy!
You won!
Pa! No bear! He's mine!
You can't have him!
Zara! Zaji!
Thank you!
Awesome! Those guys are amazing!
Bravo! Bravo!
Oh, man! I've moved to tears!
Give it your best in the third round, too!
Shadda!
Who's Shadda you on anyway, you traitors?
I can't believe this thing!
I can't believe this!
Nobody's ever beaten the Groggy Monsters!
Oh, hi, Raph! Wakey Wakey!
Hey! You better make your call!
Go ahead! Here!
Oh, thank you!
Yeah, that last move was a flagrant foul
if I've ever seen one!
He's out of the game!
And that's the final whistle!
There you have it, folks!
The Groggy Ring Match is officially over!
They did it!
I can't stop!
Crying!
Nice work! You're a real pro!
It's the end of an era!
The Groggy Monsters have finally been dethroned
as the kings of the ring!
The two champions and winners of the second round
are Zoro and Sanji of the Straw Hat Pirates!
What'd you think would happen?
Like our guys would never lose to you!
Hey, Nami!
Hey, Robin!
Was I great?
Huh? Was I?
You were just wonderful!
You're nothing but a jerk!
Don't scare me like that!
Hey, hey!
Stop!
I'm so glad you followed my plan after all!
You really think you had something to do with this?
Now!
As I'm sure you all know,
at the end of our fight,
our winners, the Straw Hat Pirates,
can claim their hard-earned prize!
Will they take a member of Foxy's crew?
Or will they take his Jolly Roger?
Either way, it's up to their captain
and their captain alone!
Now!
Drum roll, please!
Well, the choice is obvious, isn't it?
You mean he's going to pick me?
I get it.
They want me, don't they?
They've wanted me this whole time!
My heart...
My heart isn't ready to say farewell yet!
Oh, no!
He's looking this way!
He's going to take me!
I know it!
I bet it'll be me.
So long, guys.
I don't want to go!
I'll put a smile on my face for my friends
even if I'm crying on the inside!
Curses!
Why do I have to be so lovable?
Come on, Luffy!
Please!
Hm.
Okay, I choose...
Hold on a sec!
What's up, Nami?
Think about it.
Their boss is probably going to take part in the next round, right?
Yeah.
We've already seen what his slow slow beam can do.
If he fights, we won't stand a chance in any game,
no matter what the rules are!
no matter what the rules are.
So the answer is obvious.
If Foxy's gonna be our biggest threat in round three,
then we should recruit him so we have the advantage.
Sure, we'd all like to get Chopper back,
but if we end up losing the next round,
then they'll probably take him right back
and our win would go to waste.
And since his crew will be dumbstruck
when they lose their precious boss,
we'll stomp him no problem and claim Chopper in round three.
Then we're guaranteed to keep him for good, get it?
No, say it isn't so!
They're really gonna take our captain away?
But that's the peanut strategy!
You guys are the lowest of the low!
Go home, lousy peanuters!
Are you afraid to fight us fair?
Although there's no rule against this strategy,
it certainly seems a bit underhanded.
A little cheating is expected of pirates,
but suddenly taking a crew's captain away
in the middle of a game
is no different than running from a fight.
Shame, shame on you straw hats,
and shame on the heartless devil of a woman
who came up with this plan.
You're truly a nefarious navigator, Nami!
How dare you talk trash about Nami!
I ought to fillet you punks!
In the long history of Davy Black fights,
no one has ever had the audacity
to pull such a lousy, no-good stunt.
So what do you say, men?
You can't call a win against the crew
with no captain of true victory, can you?
No!
after swearing on Davy Jones' name,
is it right to throw away your honor as a pirate
just to win a match?!
No!
Ha ha ha!
Why are they so mean?
Well, even if it doesn't go against the rules,
it does seem to go against some of their pirate sensibilities.
Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!
Shut up! You guys are making me mad!
I'm with Nami on this one!
I don't know. I think they're right.
Nami, why don't you grow a backbone?
You're just making a big fuss because you lost!
How about you shut up and deal with it?
Yes, ma'am, we're sorry!
Underhanded witch, though she is, the girl is right.
Monkey D. Loopy is the captain of the winning team,
so it's up to him to decide how this battle will unfold.
That is to say, he's free to choose anyone he likes,
including Foxy himself!
This is it.
He's picking me for sure.
It's not so bad.
I'm sure I'll have fun sailing with them.
No matter how you slice it,
I'm the only choice that makes sense.
Oh, look at me!
Please!
I know I'm handsome, but I don't want to go!
So they're gonna pick me, huh?
I knew these guys were cool.
Can I leave my friends behind?
How will they go on without me?
Oh, no!
How is Foxy ever gonna replace me?
Straw-head, you little punk!
You're really going to choose me, aren't you?
Yes, it's obvious.
That was probably your plan all along.
Farewell, Foxy Pirates.
Farewell, my wonderful crew.
I'll say goodbye with a smile on my face.
I owe you that much, at least.
If having such a charming personality
and stunning looks is a sin,
then I accept my punishment.
Those poor straw hats really need a poster boy for their crew.
I can't blame them for wanting me.
I can't blame anyone for wanting me.
Say, just a quick thought.
That plan of yours,
although it would give us a big advantage,
you realize it would also make Foxy a part of our crew.
Uh...
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
Oh!
Our sweet captain's heart has been crushed
under the weight of those cruel words!
It's one thing to turn him down,
but did they have to do it like that?
Aw!
It's okay!
Even if they don't want you, we still do!
You're always welcome here!
Do you mean it?
Nobody makes fun of our boss and gets away with it!
Yeah, you'll see!
We'll get him next round!
We won't let you down, boss!
I promise!
We love you!
You're leaving!
You guys!
Thank you!
I promise I'll never leave!
You're the only crew for me!
Cut the crap, will ya?
Now that the straw hats are done emotionally abusing our boss,
it's time for them to make their decision!
Come on!
Don't leave us in suspense any longer!
Fine!
In that case, there's someone I want to take back!
Shelly!
Huh?
What a turn of events!
The captain of the straw hats has chosen Shelly,
a horse that Captain Foxy picked up on a whim
after coming to this island!
Is this pure genius or just plain ASE?
Do you have any idea what you did?
Shelly!
Shelly!...
Yeah!
Shelly!
Well, guess I can't blame him.
Yeah, that is totally what I would have done.
Let me repay your kindness by treating you to some cheese back at my house.
Not in a million years!
It's your loss. Suit yourself.
Shelly says thanks, too.
Just keep off the stilts, okay?
Are you sure about this, though?
What about your little reindeer friend?
Yeah, you jerk.
How do you think he feels being left with those weirdos?
Poopy.
Poor little guy.
Chopper, I'm sorry.
I know this is hard on you, but no matter what,
I promise we'll win the next game and get you back.
So hang on a little longer, okay?
I know you can take it.
After all, you're a man, right?
You bet I am!
That's our Chopper.
Leave it to me, little pal.
You'll be just fine.
If you're Chopper's last hope, he's screwed.
I wonder what the next game's going to be.
Whatever it is, I'm ready for it.
We're gonna have Chopper back in no time!
You bet I'm gonna haverich.
I know.
We have the genius to share we've seen.
We're doing it again.
We have the highest value to see.
We've seen him.
We have the highest memory, everyone, left me.
We've seen him before we run.
各国のデッキの興奮を持っています。
On the next One Piece, round three, the round and round roller race, I'm going to be king of the pirates!